Okay, hopefully you gave that a shot.
Um, I'm going to start walking through
the solution now. All right, so the
first thing you want to do is it says
create a new HTML file. The way you do
that is you click this little plus icon
or you could come up to the top and
click file, new file. I prefer to click
the plus icon. So I'm going to click the
plus icon and I'm going to call this a
new hope.html.
And I'm going to hit enter. Now we've
got a new hope.html.
Coming back over to our instruction
sheet, it says insert the starter HTML.
There are two ways to do this. You could
type HTML
5 and hit enter and that'll enter in all
the HTML. Or you can just put the
exclamation mark, hit enter, and that
will enter in all of the HTML. So now
you've got your starter code going. So
we're going to save a new hope.html.
Come back over to our instructions. So
now it says insert JavaScript. If we
want to have JavaScript, then we need to
put a script tag inside of the body. So,
we're going to type script. And now we
have our script tag. We'll save that.
We'll come over to a new hope.txt. Says
create a variable that contains the text
of the opening crawl. So, I'm going to
say opening.
So, you create a variable by using the
keyword let. Say let opening crawl
equal. And then I'm going to put quotes
and I'm going to come over here. I'm
going to copy all of the text of the
opening crawl. If you don't have this
text easily accessible, you can um copy
and paste
from Google search. So, this is the
opening crawl. Um because strings are
designed to be one line, we're going to
put it all on one line. And I'm actually
going to pause the recording while I do
that. Okay, I have now put it all onto
one line. So, that is our opening crawl.
Let's come back over to a new hope.
Create a variable that contains the text
of the opening cross. So all of this we
have completed. So now we need to find
the position of the text civil war.
So I know that it's here, but I don't
really want to count that out and you
shouldn't because you need to use that
in a moment. So what we're going to do
is we're going to create a variable that
finds the text of the opening crawl. So,
I'm going to create a comment here that
just says um base text. So, now I know
that this next line contains the base
text. Now, I'm going to create a comment
that says find the position of civil
war.
And so, what we're going to do is we're
going to say let um civil war
position. I'm going to put POS for
short. And I'm going to say equals
opening crawl dot search. And that will
help me find the text civil war
inside of the opening crawl. Let's test
this and see if it gives me back
anything. So
we'll put an alert. We'll save
and
we'll go live. And we get 18. So it says
18 is the position of civil war.
Let's come back over and now so we now
we have found the position of Civil War.
So now we're going to use that position
based on our next instruction using the
position alert the full text Civil War.
So Civil War is 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
characters. So let's alert that. Um, the
way we can do that is we can say alert
and then we're going to find the opening
crawl and then we're going to do substr.
The starting position is the civil war
position and the ending position is
I counted and I forgot 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
9. So it's nine characters. So we'll
give it a length of nine. And let's just
see if that gives us civil war. So,
we'll save and we'll come back over and
we get the text Civil War. So, we know
that's working.
Um, so I'm going to actually put those
two lines together and say find the
position of Civil War and alert the
text.
Now, I'm going to come back over to my
instructions. Um,
so we've used a position to alert the
text. Grab it is and print it out using
your preferred method. So,
um, I've already used substr, um, right
here. So, I'm going to use substring
this time. So, I'm going to say alert
opening opening crawl
dot substring. Um, it is is the first
two words. So, we're going to start at
the zero position and I'm going to go in
0 1 2 3 4 5 because it does not include
the last position. So I is in the zero,
T is in the one, the space is in the
two, I is in the three, S is in the
four, and I want to include the space.
So because it doesn't include the last
character. So the space is in the fifth
position. So we'll say alert zero
through position five, but don't include
position five. So that'll just be the it
is. So now, if we save this and we come
over to our document, we get the alert
civil war, and then we get the alert it
is. So we've successfully done that. So
coming back over to a new hope, we have
um grabbed it is and printed it out
using our preferred method. Now we need
to replace the text Galactic Empire with
an evil organization of your choosing.
All right. So let's replace that. So,
we're going to say opening crawl
dotreplace
and we want to place the galactic
empire
with the text
Irram Empire.
Um, all right. And then we want to So,
let's come back over and just double
check it says replace the text Galactic
Empire with the name of an eagle
organization of your choosing. Alert the
adjusted opening crawl. So, I'm going to
save this real quick and I'm going to
say let adjusted opening crawl equal the
opening crawl where we've replaced
Galactic Empire with Viltro Empire.
Um, and then let's just alert this
adjusted opening crawl to see what's
happening. So, we'll save that. We'll
come over to our website. We get Civil
War, which was uh part one, and then we
get it is which was the second part. And
then we get it is a period of civil war.
Rebel starship striking from a hidden
base have won their first victory
against the evil Viltro Empire. Uh so
we've successfully replaced that and
changed the way the opening crawl reads.
So now let's go look at the next thing
we're asked to do. Um oh the last thing
we're supposed to do is comment our name
in a program description at the top of
the file and use clean comments
throughout our code. So let's um put our
name at the top of the file. Um I'm
going to enter down. You could hit uh
command or control slash to put in a
comment. Or you could uh put in the
little carrot sign, then an exclamation,
and two dashes, and that will put in a
comment. My name is Toapita.
Description.
Um, this code adjusts the opening crawl
and pulls text out of it.
adjusts a new hopes opening crawl and
pulls text out of it. Um, I've commented
the base text. I've commented finding
the position of Civil War. Um, I'm going
to comment this line and say graph the
first two words.
And then here I'm going to say create a
new opening draw with Viltro Empire
instead. And then down here, we'll add a
last comment that says, uh, show
show the new opening crawl. And we'll
save that. And that wraps up the
solution. Um, hope you're able to follow
along. Thanks for watching.